Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions PE.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- P, 1920-2008; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Piano and Organ Workers' International Union of America, undated (Box 33)
  - Police Benevolent Association, 1985-1990, undated (Box 33)
  - Post Office Engineering Union (Great Britain), 1963 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Postal, Telegraph and Telephone International, 1920, 1962-1975 (Box 34, Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Postal, Telegraph and Telephone International, 1975-1978 (Box 34)
  - Postal, Telegraph and Telephone International, 1981, undated (Box 34)
  - Postal Telegraph Employees Association, 1926 (Box 34)
  - Printers and Publishers Employees Union, undated (Box 34)
  - Printing and Kindred Trades Federation (London, England), 1946 (Box 34)
  - Professional Air Traffic Controllers Organization, 1980-1982, undated (Box 34)
  - Professional Household Workers Union, 1972 (Box 34)
  - Professional Public Health Nurse Association, 1961 (Box 34)
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York (CUNY), 1969-1972, 2001 (Box 34, Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York (CUNY), 1973-1978 (Box 34)
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York (CUNY), 1980-1982 (Box 34)
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York (CUNY), 1987 (Box 34)
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York (CUNY), 1990-1994, undated (Box 34)
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York (CUNY): New Caucus, 1997-2000, undated (Box 34)
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York (CUNY): Unity Caucus I, 1971-1975, undated (Box 34)
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York (CUNY): Unity Caucus II, 1971-1975, undated (Box 34)
  - Progressive Mine Workers of America, Circa 1940 (Box 34)
  - Progressive Mine Workers of America. District 1, 1942 (Box 34)
  - Progressive Mine Workers of America: Women's Auxiliary, 1933 (Box 34)
  - Progressive Sheet Metal Workers Benevolent Association, Inc., 1935 (Box 34)
  - Public Services International, 1973, undated (Box 34)
  - Puerto Rico Teachers Union (Federacion de Maestros de Puerto Rico) (FMPR), 2008 (Box 34)
- Q, 1929-1977; 1 linear foot in 1 record carton
  - Quarry Workers' International Union of North America, 1929 (Box 34)
  - Quebec Federation of Labour (Federation des Travailleurs du Quebec) (Canada) I, 1971-1977 (Box 34)
  - Quebec Federation of Labour (Federation des Travailleurs du Quebec) (Canada) II, 1971-1977 (Box 34)
  - Queensland Trades and Labour Council (Australia), 1946 (Box 34)
- R, 1885-2004; 205 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1938-1978 (Box 34)
  - Railroads and Railroad Employees: General, 1902-1978 (Box 34)
  - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1960-1975 (Box 34)
  - Railway Mail Association (U.S.), 1941 (Box 34)
  - Regulator Employees Association, 1954 (Box 34)
  - Retail Cigar Clerks Union: Local 874, 1938 (Box 34)
  - Retail Clerks International Association, 1950-1964 (Box 34)
  - Retail Clerks International Association: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1939-1967 (Box 34)
  - Retail Clerks International Association: Local 888, 1975 (Box 35)
  - Retail Clerks International Association: Local 1245 (Retail Food Clerks), 1962 (Box 35)
  - Retail Clerks International Protective Association, 1935, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Retail Clerks International Union, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Retail Clerks Union, undated (Box 35)
  - Retail, Dry Goods and Chain Store Employees Union: Local 1102, 1963 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Chain Store Food Employees Union Local 338, 1944 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1946-1992 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Constitution, 1946-1962 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Constitution, 1966-1986 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Convention, 1954-1970 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 1-S Agreements I, 1949-1976 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 1-S Agreements II, 1949-1976 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 1-S Agreements III, 1949-1976 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 1-S Constitution and By-Laws, 1949-1968 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 1-S Department Store Workers Union (New York, NY), 1954-1993, undated (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 1-S Shop Stewards Convention, 1962-1978 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 3 (New York, NY), 1980-1988, undated (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 65, 1946-1947, undated (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 338, 1961-2004, undated (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 830 (New York, NY), 1947 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 1250 (Department Store Employees Union): Litigation, 1949 (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Local 1283 (Fraternal, Trade Union and Law Office Workers), 1954-1958, undated (Box 35)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU): Stewards, 1946, undated (Box 35)
  - Ring Twisters', Yarn Finishers' and Web Drawers' Association, 1941 (Box 35)
  - Riverside Wheelmen of New York, 1889 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Rochester Central Labor Union, 1885 (Box 35)
- S, 1891-2008; 4.75 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Sailors' Union of the Pacific, 1946-1947, undated (Box 35)
  - Sailors' Union of the Pacific: Agreements, 1937-1943 (Box 35)
  - Sailors' Union of the Pacific: Agreements, 1945-1947 (Box 35)
  - Salaried Employees Association, 1945 (Box 35)
  - Sawmill and Forest Workers' Union, 1971 (Box 35)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1937-1976 (Box 35)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1980-1983 (Box 35)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1988-1993, undated (Box 35)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Constitution and By-Laws, 1975-1993 (Box 35)
  - Screen Extras Guild, 1954-1989 (Box 36)
  - Screen Publicists Guild of New York, 1942 (Box 36)
  - Sculptors Guild (New York, NY), undated (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of Canada, 1963, undated (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1938-1953 (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1972-1977 (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America, undated (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America: Agreements, 1939-1942 (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America: Agreements, 1946-1947 (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America: Atlantic and Gulf District, 1945-1980, undated (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America: Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes and Inland Waters District, undated (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America: Democratic Union Organizing Committee Local 777 (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America: Harry Lundberg School: Labor Union History, 1970-1975, undated (Box 36)
  - Seafarers' International Union of North America: Pacific District, 1965 (Box 36)
  - Seamen's Union of Australia, 1948 (Box 36)
  - Secondary School Teachers Association of New York, Inc., 1960-1962, undated (Box 36)
  - Sergeants Benevolent Association (New York, NY), 1968-1981, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1980-1984, undated (Box 36, Box 49, Folder 18, Box Shared Tamiment 187, Folder 15)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1985-1989 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1991-1999, 2006 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Civil and Human Rights Department, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Clerical Division, 1986 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Constitutions, 1960, 1988 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Department of Research, 1977-1987 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): District 925, 1981-1982, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Education Department, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Joint Council No.8 of Southern California, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 22 (Sacramento, CA), 1987, 1995 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32B-32J (New York, NY), 1970-1988 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32B-32J (New York, NY), 1991-2003, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 50C (St. Louis, MO), undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 74 (School and Library Employees) (New York, NY), 1970-1996, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 144 (Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Service Employees Union) (New York, NY), 1978-1982 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 144 (Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Service Employees Union) (New York, NY), 1983-1995, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 155 (Exterminators, Fumigators and Termite Workers Union), 1981, undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 246 (New York City Local), 1969 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 250, 1985-1986 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 284 (School Service Employees), 1992 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 300 (Civil Service Forum), 1968, 1990 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 390 (United Public Employees) (Oakland, CA), 1982 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 399 (Hospital and Service Employees Union), 1991 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 400 (San Francisco, CA), 1977 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 444, 1968 (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 509 (Dorchester, MA), undated (Box 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 525: Justice for Janitors Organizing Committee, 1987 (Box 37)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 715, 1980 (Box 37)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 767 (Hospital Workers Union) (Hyannis, MA), 1989-1991 (Box 37)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): McFadden, Ophelia, 1999 (Box 37)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): New York State Service Employees Council, 1980 (Box 37)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): United Healthcare Workers West, 2008 (Box 37)
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1958 (Box 37)
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1963-1994 (Box 37)
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Association, undated (Box 37)
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Association: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1931-1978 (Box 37)
  - Shipwrights' Union of Brooklyn, 1891 (Box 37)
  - Shirt, Waist and Laundry Workers' International Union, undated (Box 37)
  - Sindicato Nacional de Trabajadores de la Educacion, 2006 (Box 37)
  - Singapore National Trades Union Congress, 1964 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union, 1963-1966 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union, 1967 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union, 1968 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union, 1969 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union, 1970-1976 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union, 1982-1998 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union, undated (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: Affiliations Committee, undated (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: Agreements and Contracts, 1964-1969, undated (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: Collective Bargaining Decisions, 1962-1969, 1974, 1990 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: Department of Welfare/Department of Social Services, 1966-1969 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: Department of Welfare: Fliers, 1964-1967, undated (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: Proposed Merger Agreement, 1968, 1969 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: Rank and File Activities, 1967-1976, undated (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: United Office and Professional Workers: Local 19, 1919-1949 (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: United Office and Professional Workers: Local 19, 1948-1952, undated (Box 37)
  - Social Service Employees Union: Welfare Local 371, 1963-1967, undated (Box 37)
  - Society of Models for Art and Education, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers (U.S.), 1983, undated (Box 37)
  - Solidarity (Poland), undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - South Bend Industrial Union Council: Racial and Religious Tolerance Committee, undated (Box 37)
  - South Wales Miners' Federation, 1912 (Box 37)
  - Southern Tenant Farmers' Union, 1973-1984, undated (Box 37)
  - Southern Trade Unions, 1956 (Box 37)
  - Southwestern Telephone Workers Union, 1940-1946 (Box 37)
  - Staff Association, National Council of Churches of Christ in the United States of America, 1986 (Box 37)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America, 1939-1946 (Box 37)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America, undated (Box 37)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America: Local 1 (New York, NY), 1940 (Box 37)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America: Local 2 (Playground Directors, New York, NY), undated (Box 37)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America: Local 28, undated (Box 37)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America: Local 128, 1941-1942 (Box 37)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America: Local 129 and Local 203, undated (Box 37)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America: Local 312, 1944 (Box 37)
  - Staionary Engineers, Firemen, Maintenance and Building Service Union: Local 670, undated (Box 37)
  - Steel and Metal Workers Industrial Union (U.S.), 1973 (Box 37)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee (U.S.), 1937-1938 (Box 37)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee (U.S.), 1938 (Box 38)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee (U.S.), 1941-1945, undated (Box 38)
  - Store, Furnace and Allied Appliance Workers' International Union of North America, 1977, 1990 (Box 38)
  - Stove Mounters International Union of North America, 1938-1943 (Box 38)
  - Subway-Surface Supervisors Association, 1978 (Box 38)
  - Supporting Staff Association of the College of Physicians and Surgeons of Columbia University, 1977, undated (Box 38)
  - Swedish Trade Union Confederation (LO) (Landsorganisationen i Sverige) I, 1961-2002, undated (Box 38)
  - Swedish Trade Union Confederation (LO) (Landsorganisationen i Sverige) II, 1961-2002, undated (Box 38)
  - Swedish Union of Local Government Officers, undated (Box 38)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America, 1919-1963, undated (Box 38)
- T, 1885-2003; 3.5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Taxi Chauffers Union of Greater New York, 1937-1947 (Box 38)
  - Taxi Drivers' Organizing Committee, 1944-1998, undated (Box 38)
  - Taxi Workers Organizing Committee (New York, NY), undated (Box 38)
  - Teachers' Representatives Union, 1973 (Box 38)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York, 1917-1949 (Box 38)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York, 1950-1959 (Box 38)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York, 1960-1974 (Box 38)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York I, undated (Box 38)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York II, undated (Box 38)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York: History and Background, 2003, undated (Box 38)
  - Teaching Assistants Association (University of Wisconsin - Madison), 1970 (Box 38)
  - Technical, Editorial and Office Assistants Union: Local 20055 (Washington, NJ), 1935 (Box 38)
  - Telecommunications International Union, 1977-1983 (Box 38)
  - Telecommunications International Union, 1986-1987 (Box 38)
  - Telecommunications Workers' Union (Canada), 1986-1988 (Box 38)
  - Telecommunications Workers' Union (Canada): Joint Committee Members' Health and Safety Handbook, 1986 (Box 38)
  - Telegraph Employees' Union, 1942-1946 (Box 38)
  - Telegraph Workers Federal Labor Union, 1943 (Box 38)
  - Telephone Employees' Organization, 1977 (Box 38)
  - Telephone Guild of Wisconsin, 1938 (Box 38)
  - Telephone Traffic Union (New York), 1946-1963, 1982 (Box 38)
  - Telephone Workers Organizing Committee, 1948, undated (Box 38)
  - Texaco Tanker Officers Association, 1961 (Box 38)
  - Texas Farm Workers Union, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Textile Workers Organizing Committee (CIO), 1937, undated (Box 38)
  - Textile Workers Strike of 1928: New Bedford, MA; Textile Mills Committee, undated (Box 38)
  - Textile Workers Trade Union of China, Peking, 1958 (Box 38)
  - Theater Project Union: Spot Lite, circa 1930s (Box 38)
  - Theatre Union (New York, NY), undated (Box 38)
  - Theatrical Mechanical Association: New York Lodge 1 (New York, NY), 1908 (Box 38)
  - Theatrical Mutual Association: New York Lodge 1 (New York, NY), 1936 (Box 38)
  - Third Avenue Railway System Employees Benefit Association, 1933-1946 (Box 38)
  - Tile, Marble, Terrazzo & Shopmen International Union of the United States and Canada, 1978 (Box 38)
  - Tile, Marble, Terrazzo, Finishers, Shopworkers and Granite Cutters International Union, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Tobacco Workers International Union, 1978-1984, undated (Box 38)
  - Tobacco Workers International Union: Constitutions, 1941-1970 (Box 39)
  - Trade Union Democracy, 1959-1967, undated (Box 39)
  - Trade Union Directories: New York City, 1937, undated (Box 39)
  - Trade Union Leadership Council, 1959-1962, undated (Box 39)
  - Trade Unions International of Land and Air Transport Workers (Bucharest, Romania), 1951 (Box 39)
  - Trade Unions International of Seamen, Inland Waterways Workers, Fishermen and Port Workers, 1950 (Box 39)
  - Trademark Society, Inc., undated (Box 39)
  - Trades and Labor Congress of Canada, 1936-1954, undated (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1885 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1919 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1920 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1924 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1925 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1926 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1927 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1928 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1930 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1934 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1935 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1936 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1938 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1939 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1942 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1943 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1945 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1947 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1948 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1950 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1953 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1954 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1957 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1958 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1960 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1961 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1964 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1967 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1980-1985 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress, 1991-2003 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress I, undated (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress II, undated (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress III, undated (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress: Education Service, 1949-1955, undated (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress (Ghana), 1966 (Box 39)
  - Trades Union Congress: Origins and Establishment of, 1955 (Box 39)
  - Transport and General Workers' Union (Great Britain), 1943, 1968, undated (Box 39)
  - Transport Workers' Minority Movement (London, England), 1928 (Box 39)
  - Transportation Communications International Union, 1987-1990, undated (Box 39)
  - Transportation Communications International Union: Constitutions, 1987 (Box 39)
  - Transportation Communications International Union: Conventions, 1987 (Box 39)
  - Travailleurs Unis de l'Automobile (TUA) (Canada), undated (Box 40)
  - Trans World Airlines (TWA) Flight Engineers Strike, 1962 (Box 40)
- U, 1832-2009; 7.5 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Unemployed and Project Workers Union (New York, NY), undated (Box 40)
  - Uniformed Sanitationmens Association: DeLury, John Joseph, 1978 (Box 40)
  - Union County Central Labor Union (Union County, NJ), 1941 (Box 40)
  - Union des Syndicalistes (Paris), undated (Box 40)
  - Union des Syndicats des Travailleurs Algeriens, 1959 (Box 40)
  - Union General de Trabajadores (Spain), 1978-1979 (Box 40)
  - Union General de Trabajadores (Spain), 1979, undated (Box 40)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE), 1995-2001 (Box 40, Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Union of Shop, Distributive and Allied Workers, 1955, 1961 (Box 40)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR), 1925-1959, undated (Box 40)
  - Union of Telephone Workers, 1948, 1974, 1983 (Box 40)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry I, 1891-1996, undated (Box 40)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry II, 1891-1996, undated (Box 40)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry: Constitutions, 1928-1966 (Box 40)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry: Constitutions, 1986-1996 (Box 40)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry: Local 2, 1966-1994 (Box 40)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry: Local 2, undated (Box 40)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry: Local 457 (Nassau County, NY), 1947 (Box 40)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry: Local 638, 1948, 1995-1996 (Box 40)
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Vehicle Workers of America: Local 17 (Oakland, CA), undated (Box 40)
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Vehicle Workers of America: Local 49 (New York, NY), 1927 (Box 40)
  - United Brick and Clay Workers of America, 1928, 1959 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Carpenter Legislative Improvement Committee, 1991 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Constitutions, 1941-1951 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Constitutions, 1963-1979 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Constitutions, 1987-1996 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Conventions, 1958 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: District Council of Nassau County, 1965-1977 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: District Council of New York City and Vicinity: Agreements and Contracts, 1950-1996 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: District Council of New York City and Vicinity: By-Laws, 1963-1990 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: District Council of New York City and Vicinity: Fliers, 1998-1999 (Box 40)